in this video we'll go over logistic
在这个视频中 我们会重温
regression this is a learning algorithm
逻辑回归 这是一种学习算法
that you use when the output labels y
使用在当监督学习的
in a supervised learning problem are all
输出标签y
either 0 or 1 so for binary
要么是0要么是1的情况下 所以对于二元
classification problems given an input
分类问题来讲 给定一个输入
feature vector X may be corresponding to
特征向量X 它可能对应
an image that you want to recognize as
一张图片 你想识别这张图片识别
either a cat picture or not a cat
看它是否是一只猫或者不是一只猫的
picture you want an algorithm that can
图片,你想要一个算法能够
output the prediction which you only
输出预测 你只能
call y hat which is your estimate of Y
称之为y冒（帽） 也就是你对实际值Y的估计
more formally you want Y hat to be the
更正式地来说 你想让y冒表示
probability or the chance the Y is equal
y等于1的一种可能性或者是机会
to 1 given the input features X so in
前提条件是给定了输入特征X
other words if X is a picture as we saw
换句话来说 如果X是我们在上个视频
in the last video you want Y hat to tell
看到的图片 你想让y冒来告诉
you what is the chance that this is a
你这是一只猫的图片的机率有多大
cat picture so X as we said in the
因此正如在之前的视频中所说的
previous video is a nx dimensional
X是一个n_x维的向量
vector given that the parameters of
逻辑回归的参数
logistic regression will be w which is
我们用W来表示 这也是一个
also an nx dimensional vector
n_x维向量
together with b which is just a real
参数里面还有b 这是一个实数
number so giving an input X and the
所以给出输入x以及
parameters w and b how do we generate
参数w和b之后 我们怎样产生
the output Y hat well one thing you
输出预测值y冒 一件
could try that doesn't work would be to
你可以尝试却不可行的事是
have Y hat be w transpose X plus b you
让y冒等于w的转置乘以x然后加上b
know kind of a linear function of the
这种关于输入x的线性函数
input X and in fact this is what you use
实际上这是你在
if you were doing linear regression but
做线性回归时所用到的 但是
this isn't a very good algorithm for
这对于二元分类问题来讲
binary classification because you want Y
不是一个非常好的算法 因为你想让y冒
hat to be the chance that Y is equal to
表示实际值y等于1的机率的话
1 so Y hat should really be between 0
y冒应该在0到1之间
and 1 and it's difficult to enforce that
这很难去实现
because w transpose x plus b can be much
因为w的转置乘以x再加上b可能
bigger than 1 or can even be negative
比1要大得多,或者甚至为一个负值
which doesn't make sense for probability
对于你想要的在0和1之间的概率来说
that you want to be between 0 & 1 so in
它是没有意义的 因此在
logistic regression our output is
逻辑回归中 我们的输出
there going to be Y hat equals the
应该是y冒等于
sigmoid function applied to this quantity
由这个式子作为自变量的sigmoid函数中
this is what the sigmoid function looks like
这是sigmoid函数的图像
if on the horizontal axis I
如果我把水平轴作为
plot Z then the function sigmoid of Z
z轴 那么关于z的sigmoid函数
look like this so it goes smoothly from
是这样的 它是平滑地
0 up to 1 let me label my axis here this
从0走向1 让我在这里标记纵轴,这
is 0 and it crosses the vertical axis at
是0 曲线与纵轴相交的截距是
0.5 so this is what sigmoid of z looks
0.5 这就是关于z的sigmoid函数的图像
like and we're going to use Z to denote
我们通常都使用z
this quantity w transpose X plus b just
来表示w的转置乘以x再加上b的值
the formula for the sigmoid function
关于sigmoid函数的公式是这样的
sigmoid of Z where Z is a real number is
在这里z是一个实数
1 over 1 plus e to the negative z so
1除以1加上e的负z次方
notice a couple of things if Z is very
这里要说明一些要注意的事情 如果z非常大
large then e to the negative Z will be
那么e的负z次方将会
close to 0 so then sigmoid of Z will be
接近于0 关于z的sigmoid函数将会
approximately 1 over 1 plus something
近似等于1除以1加上某个
very close to 0 because you know e to
非常接近于0的项 因为e的指数
negative of the very large number will
如果是个绝对值很大的负数的话 这项将会
be close to 0 so this is close to 1
接近于0 所以这个接近1
and indeed we if you look on the plots
实际上如果你看左边的图
on the left if Z is very large then
如果z很大的话那么
sigmoid of Z it is very close to 1
关于z的sigmoid函数会非常接近1
conversely if Z is very small or it is a
相反地 如果z非常小或者说
very large negative number then sigmoid
是一个绝对值很大的负数 那么关于z的sigmoid函数
of z becomes 1 over 1 plus e to the
就是1除以1加上e的负z次方
negative Z and this becomes its a huge
这项变成一个很大的数
number so this becomes you know think of
你可以认为这是
it as 1 over 1 plus a number that is
1除以1加上一个
very very big and so that's close to 0
非常非常大的数 所以这个就接近于0
and indeed you see that as Z becomes a
实际上你看到当z变成一个
very large negative number sigmoid of z
绝对值很大的负数 关于z的sigmoid函数
you know goes very close to 0 so when
就会非常接近于0 因此当
you implement logistic regression your
你实现逻辑回归时 你的
job is to try to learn parameters w and
工作就是去让机器学习参数w以及b
b so that Y hat becomes a good estimate
这样才使得y冒成为对y=1这一情况的概率
of the chance of Y being equal to 1
的一个很好的估计
before moving on just another note on
在继续进行之前 在符号上要注意的另一点是
the notation when we program neural
当我们对神经网络进行编程时
networks will usually keep the parameter w
经常会让参数w
and prameter b separate we're here b
和参数b分开 在这里
corresponds to the interceptor  in
参数b对应的是一种偏置
some of the classes you might have seen
在某些课程里 你可能已经见过
a notation that handles this differently
处理这个问题时的其他符号表示
in some conventions you define an extra
比如在某些例子里 你定义一个额外的特征
feature called x0 and with that equal to
称之为x_0 并且使它等于1
one so that now X is in R of nx plus
那么现在x就是一个n_x加1维的变量
one and then you define Y hat to be
然后你定义y冒等于
equal to Sigma of theta transpose X in
θ的转置乘以x这个项 的sigmoid函数
this alternative notational convention
在这个备选的符号惯例里
you have a vector parameters theta theta
你有一个参数向量θ θ_0
0 theta 1 theta 2 down to theta nx
θ_1 θ_2直到θ_n_x
and so theta 0 plays the role of b
这样θ_0就充当了b
that's just a real number and theta 1
这是一个实数
down to theta nx play the role of w
而剩下的θ_1直到θ_n_x充当了w
it turns out when you implement your
结果就是当你实现你的
neural network will be easier to just
神经网络时 有一个比较简单的方法是
keep B and W as separate parameters and
保持b和w分开
so in this class we will not use any of
因此在这节课里我们不会使用任何
this notational convention that I just
这类符号惯例 就是我刚
wrote in red if you've not seen this
用红笔写的,如果你在之前
notation before in other classes don't
的其他课程里没有见过这类符号记法,不要
worry about it it's just that for those
担心 只是对于那些
of you that have seen this notation I
已经见过这类符号记法的人
wanted to mention explicitly that we're
我想明确地提一下 也就是我们
not using that notation in this course
在这节课里不用像这样的符号记法
but if you've not seen this before is
但是你之前没有见过的话就
not important and you don't need to
无所谓了 你不需要去
worry about it so you've now seen what
担心 现在你已经知道
the logistic regression model looks like
逻辑回归模型是什么样子了
next to train the parameters w and b you
下一步要做的是训练参数w和b
need to define a cost function let's do
你需要定义一个代价函数 让我们在
that in the next video
下节课里对其进行解释